justify-content : 
this CSS property aligns items horizontally and accepts the following values:-

flex-start: Items align to the left side of the container.
flex-end: Items align to the right side of the container.
center: Items align at the center of the container.
space-between: Items display with equal spacing between them.
space-around: Items display with equal spacing around them.

Note : when the flex direction is a column, justify-content changes to the vertical and align-items to the horizontal.


align-items :
This CSS property aligns items vertically and accepts the following values:-

flex-start: Items align to the top of the container.
flex-end: Items align to the bottom of the container.
center: Items align at the vertical center of the container.
baseline: Items display at the baseline of the container.
stretch: Items are stretched to fit the container.


flex-direction :
This CSS property defines the direction items are placed in the container, and accepts the following values:-

row: Items are placed the same as the text direction.
row-reverse: Items are placed opposite to the text direction.
column: Items are placed top to bottom.
column-reverse: Items are placed bottom to top.

UserWidgetComponent